<resources>
    <string name="app_name">goBiz</string>

    <string name="hint_name">Name</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_pass">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_confirm_pass">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with">Sign in with</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_image_button">Facebook Login - Image Button</string>
    <string name="email_id">Email Id</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_your_details">Forgot your details?</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="txt_sign_up">Enter Your Details</string>
    <string name="dashboard_title">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="course_label">Courses</string>
    <string name="badges_label">Badges</string>
    <string name="network_label">Network</string>
    <string name="profile_label">Profile</string>
    <string name="settings_label">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_label">About</string>
    <string name="goto_dashboard">Goto Dashboard</string>
    <string name="send_reset_link">Send Reset Link</string>
    <string name="course_item_title">Course %1$s: %2$s</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_story_intro">Zara and Anwar have both been thinking about starting a new business. Zara is considering three different options: opening a tailoring shop, a clothing shop, or a jewelry shop. Anwar has also identified three different ideas: opening a restaurant, a bakery, or a coffee shop. They discuss their ideas together.</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_story_intro_caption">Story of Zara and Anwar</string>
    <string name="story">Story</string>
    <string name="lesson_1">Lesson 1</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_dialogue_1">\"I think that it will be complicated and expensive to find all the tools and materials to make jewelry. What do you think, Anwar?\"</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_dialogue_2">\"I think that people need clothes more than jewelry.\"</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_dialogue_3">\"You are right. It is probably better to open a clothing shop.\"</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_dialogue_4">\"I am experienced in banking, but I don\'t feel skilled enough to open a restaurant.\"</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_dialogue_5">\"Everyone needs to buy bread every day. Why not open a bakery?\"</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_story_question_1">What are Zara and Anwar trying to decide?</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_story_question_2">What factors are they considering when deciding on a business idea?</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_story_question_3">What business idea do you think Zara and Anwar should each choose?</string>
    <string name="consider_the_following_questions_before_moving_on_slide_to_reveal">Consider the following \nquestions before moving on.\nSlide to reveal:</string>
    <string name="theory_model_subheader">Theory/Model</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_theory_model">Most successful new businesses address two related issues – one is an unmet customer need; the second is a new idea for meeting this need, either a new business approach or a new technology. For your business idea to work, you should try to consider both items. \n\nTake for example good quality coffee shops. Previously in many countries, coffee was not a luxury item, it was sold in restaurants or on street corners by vendors at low price. But as people have gotten wealthier, demand for quality coffee, a small luxury, has grown; meanwhile, some entrepreneurs spotted this new unmet need and came up with a new business model, providing quality coffee in comfortable environments – and successful cafes have sprouted up all over. \n\nTo come up with a business idea, try to think of: \n- What people need or want but don’t have. \n- Resources that you have access to and could use. \n- Your own strengths, talents and interests. \n- A problem you have experienced or observed, and for which you think you have a solution. \n\nAlways make sure these two things go together – Unmet customer needs and new, innovative solutions.</string>
    <string name="theory_model">Theory/Model</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_examples_caption">Unmet Needs to Solutions</string>
    <string name="example_slide_to_reveal_instruction"><![CDATA[Slide to reveal examples of unmet needs & solutions]]></string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_unmet_need_1">Good quality coffee</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_unmet_need_2">Healthy fast food</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_solution_1">Italian espresso \nin a/c café</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_solution_2">Natural ingredient roadside restaurant/food stand</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_unmet_need_3">Low cost stylish clothes</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_solution_3">T-shirts designed by local young artists, silk screened</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_unmet_need_4">Fast Khmer translation</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_solution_4">Online service 24/7</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_unmet_need_5">Tourists want local \'experience\'</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_solution_5">Customized tours involving local community</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_unmet_need_6">Wedding party food</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_example_solution_6">Baking service delivered by moto</string>
    <string name="exercise">Exercise</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_exercise_instructions">To find a good business idea, do the following:</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_exercise_part_1">On one side of a piece of paper 5 or 10 unmet needs you know about – things you wish you had in your everyday life, or that people you know have mentioned – like good quality coffee (or low priced t-shirts, or designer candles…).</string>
    <string name="lesson">Lesson</string>
    <string name="continued">(continued)</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_exercise_part_2">Then, on the other side of the paper, try coming up with solutions to these unmet needs, innovative things that could be done to address them.</string>
    <string name="bringing_it_back">Bringing it Back</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_bringing_it_back_instructions">Think back to the four points raised earlier - What people need but don\'t have. Resources that you have and could use. Your own strengths and interests. A problem you can solve.</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_bringing_it_back_prompt">Which unmet need / solution do you think fits you and your opportunities best? Type that business idea below, along with the customer needs that it meets. Your answers will be saved.</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_bringing_it_back_question_1">Potential Customers\' Unmet Needs:</string>
    <string name="lesson_1_bringing_it_back_question_2">Business Idea / Solution to Meet this Need:</string>
    <string name="edit_text_hint">|</string>
</resources>
